要是阿鸡和阿鸭生个小宝宝该有多酷
Hey. Wouldn't it be cool if our duck and our chick had a baby?
可以叫它查克
We could call it Chuck.
或狄克[老二的双关语]
Or Dick.
我要请你们帮忙
Listen, I-I need a favor.
我刚才洗澡  正当我...
I was in the shower, and as I was...
洗身体时  感觉到了点什么
...cleansing myself, I ah, I-I, well I felt something.
是不是很像打喷嚏  只是感觉更爽
Was it like a sneeze, only better?
不是  不是  是我身上长了东西
No, no, I mean, I mean a thing on my body.
什么东西
Well, what was it?
不晓得  它长在我不能...
Well, I don't know. It's kind of in a place that's not....
看到的地方
It's not visually accessible to me.
我想麻烦你们
And I was hoping maybe you guys could...
帮我看一下
...could help me out.
不要
No!
拜托  又没什么
Come on, you guys! It's no big deal!
是什么  是痣吗
Well, what is it? Is it a mole?
不是  太皱了  不是痣
No, it's too wrinkly to be a mole.
那是什么 小脓包吗
Well, eww. What? Is it a pimple?
不是  它
No, it's...
比小脓包高级
...fancier than a pimple.
-罗斯  为什么你不去看医...  -你们在干...
- Look Ross, why don't you just go see a... - Guys, what's?
好吧  确定了
Okay, well, it's definite.
离冬天还有两星期
Two more weeks of winter.
-没错  -对啊
- Yeah. - Right.
这是那间咖啡馆
And this is the coffeehouse.
我都在这里演奏
This is where I play my music.
-漂亮  -是啊  他们是我的朋友
- Good deal. - Yeah. These are my friends.
各位  这是文斯  文斯  我的朋友们
People? This is Vince. Vince, the people.
文斯是消防员
Vince is a fireman.
你之前从燃烧的大楼里救过人吗
Have you ever rescued anyone from a burning building before?
救人九十八次  队上第一多
Ninety-eight hot saves. Highest on the force.
要是乔伊和我玩火柴
If Joey and I play with matches,
就可以让你累积到一百
we could get you up to an even 100.
孩子  不能拿火灾开玩笑
Fire safety is not a joke, son.
你说得对  我知道
You're right. I know.
我要走了  晚上要值班
Look, I gotta go. I'm on call tonight.
-星期六见  -好的
- See you Saturday. - Okay.
菲比  他好可爱
WOW. He's cute, Pheebs.
但你不是刚和那个幼儿园老师开始交往吗
But I thought you just started dating that Kindergarten teacher.
-杰森吗  -是啊
- Oh, Jason? - Yeah.
对啊  我们今晚要去约会
Yeah, uh-huh, we're seeing each other tonight.
菲比
Well, Pheebs?
脚踏两条船  你不像这种人
Two dates in one day? That's so unlike you.
我知道  我就像在游戏人间
I know, I know! I'm like playing the field. Y'know?
我把两男人玩弄于股掌间  跟他们谈情说爱
I'm juggling two guys. I'm sowing my wild oats.
这样好像谈情说爱  游戏人间的花心萝卜
You know, this kind of, like, oat-sowing, field-playing juggler.
菲比  他们知道对方的存在吗
So Pheebs, do they know about each other?
狗狗念书时  嘴唇会动吗
Does a dog's lips move when he reads?
不  他们不知道
Okay, no, they don't know.
各位
Hey, guys.
-怎么样  -医生怎么说
- Well? - Okay, how'd it go at the doctor's?
他说完全没必要担心  绝对是良性的
He said there's definitely nothing to worry about. It's totally benign.
-是什么  -他根本说不出来
- What is it? - He couldn't even tell me.
他说是皮肤的一种
Well, it's in the skin family.
更糟的是他说  他说由于无法辨认
And the worst thing is he-he-he said, he said, without being able to identify it,
他不愿意为我切除
... he was reluctant to remove it.
你应该去找我的医生
Y'know what? You should go to my guy,
我因为长了第三个乳头去找他时
Because when I went in there with my third nipple...
他直接就把它给切了
...he just lopped it right off.
我蛮幸运的
So I guess I'm lucky.
虽然比不上天生就长两个乳头的人
I mean, not as lucky as people who are born with two nipples.
至少他们知道你长的是什么
At least they knew what yours was. You know?
你的有名字
Yours had a name.
也许医学界会以你命名那东西
Maybe they'll name yours after you.
把它称为"罗斯"
You know? They'd call it "The Ross."
以后大家会说"哟  他长了一个罗斯"
And then people would be, like, "Oh,he's got a Ross."
是啊  真酷
Yeah, that'd be cool.
彼特要跟我分手
Pete's breaking up with me.
什么
What?
我刚才听留言
I just checked my messages.
他说等他从亚特兰大回来"我们得谈一谈"
He said that when he gets back from Atlanta, "We need to talk."
-然后呢  -就这样
- And? - Well, that's it.
没有人会随便说"我们得谈一谈"
People never say, "We need to talk,"
除非是坏事
unless it's something bad.
那不一定代表他要跟你分手
That doesn't necessarily mean he's breaking up with you.
真的吗
Really?
真的  也许他只是对你不忠
Yeah. Maybe he just cheated on you.
我知道我会一直做下去 但我得告诉你
and I know I'll never miss doing it, but I gotta tell you,
知道自己能改变一个孩子的人生  真的很棒
it's pretty cool knowing that you're making a difference in a kid's life.
真好
That is so great.
天啊
Oh, my God!
-赶快通知消防队  -不行不行
- We'd better call the fire department. -  No! No!
-为什么不行  -不必找消防员吧
- No, no?  -Well, we don't need a fireman.
-应该找个能干的修理工来  -什么
- We need, like, a good mechanic. - What?
天啊  他们来了  我们快逃
Oh my God! Here they come! We gotta get out of here!
等一下  为什么
Wait. Why?
要是我想看消防员  我会直接找一个约会
If I wanted to see a fireman, I'd date one.
其实很简单  就是个多出来的乳头
That's all it is. A third nipple.
很普通的第三个乳头
You know? Just your run-of-the-mill third nipple.
你可以把它切掉  直接切掉
You can take it off. Just slice that baby right off.
把上衣脱掉让我看一下什么情况
Take your shirt off. Let's see what we're dealing with.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
让你看那个非常普通
Just showing you my run-of-the-mill,
可以直接切掉的第三个乳头
slice-it-right-off third nipple.
这不是第三个乳头
Well, that's not a third nipple.
首先  它长在屁股上
First of all, it's on your ass.
不然是什么
Well, then what is it?
等一下  别动
Wait a minute. Hold it.
-詹森  来一下  -我跟汉弥顿说话呢
- Johnson! Will you come in here a moment? - I'm with Hamilton!
他对怪东西很在行  叫他也来
He's good with weird things. Bring him in too.
我得去帮彼特浇花
I gotta go water Pete's plants.
老实说
You know what?
如果他要跟我分手  那我就不去浇了
If he's gonna break up with me, maybe I won't water his plants.
如果他要跟你分手
If he's gonna break up with you,
干脆让乔伊和我去给他"浇花"吧
maybe Joey and I should water his plants...
懂我的意思吧
...if you know what I mean.
或者...
Or...
我们可以去他家  对着花盆撒尿
we could go over there and pee on them.
我受不了了
I can't take it, you know.
我好怕跟一个人约会时  被另一个人逮个正着
I'm just, always afraid one of them is gonna catch me with the other one.
我快疯了
It's making me crazy!
何不跟其中一个分手
Why don't you break up with one of them?
你不是在游戏人间吗
What ah, what happened to playing the field?
现在...现在不像游戏了
Well, it just, it doesn't feel like playing anymore.
比较像工作  我好像在干苦力
It's feels like work. It's like I'm working in the field.
菲比  那就选一个
So Pheebs, pick one of them.
对啊  你比较喜欢哪一个
Yeah. Which one do you like more?
文斯很棒  他是男人中的男人  你们懂吧
Well, Vince is great, y'know `cause, he's like a guy, guy. Y'know?
他好壮  真的好壮
He's just so burly, so very burly.
好  那就选文斯吧
Okay, good. So there you go. Go with Vince.
但是杰森好感性
But Jason's really sensitive.
-感性很重要  选他  -也是
- Sensitive is important. Pick him. - Yeah.
是啊  听娘娘腔的话
Oh, sure. Go with the sissy.
-杰森才不娘娘腔  -不不不
- Jason is not a sissy. - Oh no-no-no-no,
我是说钱德勒
I meant Chandler.
你们知道吗  我晚上约了人吃饭
You know, I have dinner plans.
谢谢各位能临时赶来
Thank you so much for coming on such a short notice.
女士们先生们  我行医二十三载
Ladies and gentlemen, I've been practicing medicine for 23 years...
现在却被难倒了
...and I'm stumped.
这里是书房
Okay, this is the den.
你们看  灯亮
All right, check this out. Lights!
灯暗一点  烂灯
All right, less lights! Bad lights!
灯灭
Lights, go away!
看到了吗  下对指令就行了
See? You just need the right command.
也可以用手调
And the dimmer switch.
他那么有钱  电视还真小
For a rich guy he's got, that's a pretty small TV.
不不不  那是视讯电话
No, no, no. That's the video phone.
但你们本不该来的   所以不要乱碰任何东西
But hey guys you're not supposed to be here,so please, do not touch anything.
宜家家具  好舒服
IKEA, this is comfortable!
这里太高级了
This place is amazing!
-那真是天下最棒的厨房  -我知道
- Oh, God! That's the nicest kitchen. - I know.
不  我说真的
No! But it's the nicest kitchen,
冰箱还会祝我今天愉快
The refrigerator told me to have a great day.
你们看  百万富翁的支票簿
Look at this! A millionaire's checkbook.
乔伊  放下
Joey, put that down.
天啊  是彼特  快出去
Oh my God! It's Pete. Okay, get out!!
-视讯电话要怎么接  -莫妮卡
- How the hell do you answer a video phone? - Monica?
原来是这样
I guess that's how.
莫妮卡  你好吗
Monica, how's it going?
很好  很好
Oh, it's good. It's good.
我就是来帮你浇花
Just here, watering the plants.
别忘了瑞秋旁边那一盆哦
Don't forget that ficus there by Rachel.
钱德勒在沙发上
Chandler's on the couch!
我看到了  你们还真不会躲啊
I see him, you guys are just the worst hiders ever.
-嗨  -你好吗
- Hi. - How you doing?
彼特  那天你说要找我谈一谈
Pete, the other day when you said you needed to talk...
请问是好消息还是坏消息
...just so I know, is it good news or bad news?
好消息  绝对是好消息
It's good news. It's definitely good news.
等一下  有另一通电话
Hold on a second, I have another call.
你好吗
How's it going?
错了  还是我
Oh no-no-no, it's still me.
没事  我这里有子画面
Ah, no it's not. I've got picture-in-picture here.
是吗  好的
Yeah? Yeah, okay.
我再回你电话
I'm gonna have to call you back later.
莫妮卡  说你呢  我再回你电话
Monica? You. I'm gonna have to call you back.
好  改天见
Okay. So I'll see you soon.
-好  我爱你  -我爱你
- Okay. I love you. - I love you.
我们也爱你
We love you too!
好啦  是好消息  是好消息
Okay. Well, it's good news. It's good news.
-你觉得是什么好消息  -你们看
- What do you think the good news is? - Well, look at this!
他开了一张五万元的支票
He wrote a check for $50,000 to
给"雨果·凌格戒指设计"
"Hugo Lindgren's Ring Design."
对不起  你觉得是什么好消息
Sorry. What do you think the good news is?
天啊
Oh, my!
莫妮卡要嫁给百万富翁了
Monica's gonna marry a millionaire!
赶快打给妈  打给妈  打给妈
You gotta get Mom on the phone! Call Mom! Call Mom!
你好
Hello.
那是彼特的妈妈
And that's Pete's mom.
莫妮卡  你们一定得办个主题婚礼
Mon you definitely have to make it a theme wedding,
主题可以是...
And the theme could be:
"看我们多有钱啊"
"Look How Much Money We've Got!"
我是说  你可以在喜帖里放钱
Y'know, I mean you could put, you could put moneyin-in the invitations!
你可以用钱做成餐具
You could have, like, little-money place settings.
第一道菜可以上钞票沙拉
And you could start with a money salad.
虽然干了点  绝对受欢迎
I mean, it'll be dry, but people will like it.
别再说了
Would you stop?
我们才交往几个星期
We've only gone out a couple of weeks.
我们还不知道他会不会求婚
I mean we don't even know if he's gonna propose.
话是这么说  但他是彼特  跟别人不一样
Yes, but this is Pete. Okay? He's not like other people,
你们第一次约会  他就带你去罗马
on your first date hetook you to Rome.
对大多数男人来说
For most guys, that's like
那是第三  第四次约会的事
a third or fourth date kind of thing.
如果他要求婚  那就太夸张了
Well, if that's what it is ,then it's crazy.
莫妮卡说得对  这可是婚姻大事  好不好
Monica's right. We're talking about getting married here. Okay?
她不能说嫁就嫁
She can't just rush into this.
你懂什么  你还娶了个女同志呢
What do you know? You married a lesbian!
我要走了  我要去跟文斯分手
I gotta go. I have to break up with Vince.
你选了那个老师
So you're going with the teacher?
是啊  我很喜欢文斯  但杰森好感性
Yeah, I like Vince a lot, y'know? But Jason is so sensitive.
但按长远来说  感性应该比...
And in the long run, I think sensitive it's just better than having just like
非常非常健美的身材要好得多
...a really, really, really nice body.
杰森  我绝对选杰森
Jason. Definitely Jason.
-祝我好运  -祝你好运
- Wish me luck! - Good luck!
万岁
Oh, my God!
对不起
Sorry.
我在想像接到钞票捧花的感觉
I was imagining what it'd be like to catch the money bouquet.
打扰一下  文斯在吗
Excuse me. Is Vince here?
在  文斯
Oh, sure. Vince.
我不晓得你们真的会从上面滑下来
I didn't know you guys actually used those.
什么事
So what's up?
这件事很难启齿
This isn't gonna be easy.
我们还是别再见面了
I don't think we should see each other anymore.
很好
Good deal.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
No, it's okay.
我还以为我们之间是有火花的
It's just that I thought we had something pretty special here.
我以为自己终于找到可以倾诉的对象
And y'know I-I felt like you were someone I could finally open up to, and...
我还有好多东西没跟你分享呢
There's so much in me I haven't shared with you yet.
天啊  我不知道你...
My God! I didn't know you were so
抱歉  我说不出话来了
I'm sorry. I can't talk.
我要去写日记
I'm gonna go write in my journal.
等一下  等一下
Wait! Wait! Wait!
我跟你说  你如果想解决那个问题
I'm telling you, if you wanna take care of that thing,
就去找我的药草师
go see my herbal guy.
谢了  菲比  我是想切除
Thanks. But I wanna remove it, Pheebs.
不是想做成香料
I don't want to make it savory.
如果女生发现情人身上长了怪东西
When girls sleep with guys with weird things on their body...
都会跟朋友广播
...they tell their friends about it.
给我
Give me that.
别生我的气  我就是忍不住
Okay, don't be mad at me, but I couldn't resist.
《新娘杂志》
Bride's Magazines?
我知道你不会答应求婚
Yes, and I know that you'd say no if he asked you,
但恕我冒昧
but I'm sorry;
穿这套唐娜·凯伦礼服走红毯
how great would you look walking down the aisle...
会有多美啊
...in this Donna Karan?
一定会很美
You so would!
不结婚也要买
You should get that anyway.
可以穿去俱乐部
Well, for clubbing.
很奇怪
It is so weird.
我说过不会答应  但是今天早上...
I know what I said. But this morning...
我躺在床上  想象着说"愿意"的感觉
...I was lying in bed,I was, I was imagining what it'd be like to say yes.
我知道有点突然  也很匆促
I know it's a little sudden, and it's rushed...
而且我完全不是会做这种事的人
and it's totally not like me to do something like this,
但这不代表我不可以  对吧
But it doesn't mean I can't. Right?
毕竟我那么爱彼特
I mean, I'm crazy about Pete.
我们追求同样的东西
And I know that we want the same things.
当我想到说"愿意"这两个字时
And when I thought about saying yes...
我觉得很快乐
...it made me really happy.
天啊
Oh, my God!
我知道
I know.
我还要派
I need more pie.
莫妮卡  要是你真的结婚
Mon, if you do get married,
我可以带两个男伴去吗
can I bring two guests?
-你没跟消防员分手吗  -没有
- You didn't break up with that fireman? - No.
我就是想通过这样告诉你们
That was my way of telling you.
原来他非常感性
Well, it turns out he's incredibly sensitive.
他写日记  还画画
He keeps a journal and he paints.
他甚至为我画了一幅炭笔肖像画
He even showed me charcoal drawings that he drew of me.
他更想用水彩画
He'd prefer watercolors,
但你也知道  他拿黑炭更方便
but y'know, he has easy access to a lot ofcharcoal.
那你要甩掉杰森吗
So then, are you going to dump Jason?
对  我总得跟其中一个分手
Well, yeah, because I have to break up with someone.
杰森很感性
So Jason is sensitive.
但现在  文斯也是
But now, so is Vince.
而文斯又有身材
Plus, Vince has the body. You know?
所以...
So....
这是纯算术问题
It's really just about the math.
-杰森  -请进
- Jason. - Yeah, come on in.
菲比  你在电话里的语气很严肃
: So Phoebe, you ah, sounded kinda serious on the phone,
-出了什么事吗  -没事
- is ah, is anything wrong? -  Nah-ha!
你一定是罗斯
You must be Ross.
我是萨吉大师
I am Guru Saj.
老实说  我没找过大师所以...
Listen, I gotta tell you,I've never been to a guru before, so....
放轻松
Well, relax.
如果能让你安心点的话  我在中部
If it makes you feel better, I've attended some of
念过最好的医学院
the finest medical schools in Central America.
来看看你的皮肤异常吧
Well, let's take a look at this skin abnormality of yours.
来吧  请坐
Come on, have a seat.
跟我想的一样  是昆度斯
As I suspected, it's a kundus.
什么是"昆度斯"
What's a "kundus"?
不晓得  对你来说是什么
I don't know. What's a kundus with you?
请趴下
Please lie down.
我有一种药膏可以让它立即缩小
I've got a salve that ought to shrink that right up.
值得一试
Okay. I guess it's worth a try.
那当然  效果应该...
Oh sure, we should see results-Whoa!!
显然不能这么做
Clearly not the way to go!
怎么了  怎么了
What? What?
我们似乎惹火它了
We appear to have angered it.
我们  我们惹火它了
We? We angered it?
我看到症结了
I think I see the problem.
恐怕我们得动用更有力的手段
And I'm afraid we're gonna have to use a much stronger tool.
爱
Love.
拜托
Oh, God!
罗斯  它绝不会轻易脱落
Ross, there is absolutely no way this is gonna come off...
除非你...
...unless you start to....
怎么了
What was, what was that?
它没了
Well, it's gone.
怎么会
How's that?
被我的手表刮掉了
Got caught in my watch.
灯光
Lights.
浪漫的灯光
Romantic lights.
真好
Nice.
我说过有事情要告诉你
So there was this thing I wanted to talk to you about.
对哦  我完全忘记这回事了
Oh, right. I'd completely forgot about that.
我最近想了很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
-我审视我的人生  -怎么了
- And I look at my life... - Yes?
觉得自己已经征服了商场
...and I feel like I've conquered the business world.
也已经征服了知识界
And I feel like I've conquered the intellectual world.
现在又拥有世界上最美的女人
And now I have the most beautiful woman in the world.
但是还有一个缺憾
But there's one thing missing.
什么缺憾
What's that?
我该征服体育界了
It's time for me to conquer the physical world.
好吧
Okay.
莫妮卡  我想成为...
Monica, I wanna become...
终极格斗冠军
...the Ultimate Fighting Champion.
你想成为什么
You wanna what?
我想成为终极格斗冠军
I wanna be the Ultimate Fighting Champion.
那是全世界最激烈的体能竞技
It's the most intense physical competition in the world.
在四十九个州被禁
It's banned in 49 states.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我的教练保志正在教我...
My trainer, Hoshi, is teaching me...
截拳道和巴西街头搏击的综合技能
a combination of Gee Koon Doe and Brazilian street fighting,
我甚至请人设计了专用的八角拳击场
I even had my own octagon training ring designed.
-所以你找的是拳击场设计师  -对
- And I suppose you used a ring designer for that. - Yes.
莫妮卡  我要你在最前排看我赢得胜利
Monica, I want you there, in the front row,when I win.
我要你近得可以闻到血腥味
I want you close enough to smell the blood.
你意下如何
What do you think?
我的父母会很高兴
My parents will be so happy.
*疯狂的内裤  爬上我的屁股*
*Crazy underwear Creeping up my butt*
*疯狂的内裤  总是一成不变*
*Crazy underwear Always in a rut*
*疯狂的内裤...*
*Crazy underwear*
天啊  他来干什么
Oh No! What is he doing here?
没关系  继续唱  继续弹
All right, just keep playing, just keep playing.
会安全过关的  不会有事的
You'll get through this. You'll be fine.
谢谢大家
Okay, thank you.
依照惯例  演唱完不要跟我说话
And as always, no one talk to me after the show.
我刚好路过  看到你今晚在表演
I was passing by and I saw that you were playing tonight,
看你在台上的感觉好棒
It's kinda cool seeingyou up there.
怎么回事  他是谁
What's going on here? Who's this guy?
我不知道  他突然跑来亲我
I don't know! He just started kissing me.
快捉住他  捉住他  文斯
Get him, get him, Vince!
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
好吧  我同时跟你们交往
Okay. I've been dating both of you.
这种感觉很差  因为...
And it's been really horrible, Cause y'know it's been
对我来说  感觉很好
a lot of fun, for me.
你们两个我都喜欢
But I like you both...
我不知道该选谁
...and I didn't know how to choose.
对不起  我很差劲
So... I'm sorry, I'm just, I'm terrible,
我是差劲的人  我差劲死了
I'm a terribleperson. I'm terrible.
菲比  别这样  没关系
Phoebe, Phoebe relax, it's okay. I mean
我们又没说  只能跟彼此交往
we never said this was exclusive.
我们也是  你别太自责了
Yeah, and neither did we. Give yourself a break.
真的吗
Really?
是啊  我们交往的时间又不长
Yeah. I mean y'know, we haven't been going out that long.
得了吧  甚至还没上过床
Come on, we haven't even slept together yet.
你们没有
You haven't?
你们有
You have?
好吧  这不关我的事了
Well, this is none of my business.
我真不敢相信  你跟他上床了
I can't believe this! You slept with him?
我陪你在公园吃过烛光晚餐啊
Well, I made you a candlelight dinner in the park.
好吧  菲比  我帮你做决定好了
Y'know Phoebe, I'm gonna make this real easy for you.
幸好场面没有太难看
That could've been really awkward.
你居然陪他在公园吃烛光晚餐
You made him a candlelight dinner in the park?
对  但我也可以陪你吃  我会陪你吃
Yeah, but I can do that for you. I'm gonna do that for you.
我无法接受自己居然跟一个...
I can't believe I went out with somebody...
在林木区点明火的人交往
...who'd have an open flame in the middle of a wooded area!
不会有事的
Everything's gonna be all right.
好吗  狄克
Okay, Dick?
你们好  我是萨吉大师
Hello. I am Guru Saj.
他本来就是只鸭子吧  否则...
That'ssupposed to be a duck right? Because otherwise...
就远超出我的能力范围了
...this is way out of my league.
是啊  他咳得很严重
Yeah, yeah. He's got a, he's got a really bad cough,
我们的兽医都治不好
and our vet, he can't doanything about it.
你有办法吗
Is there something you can do?
我看看
Let me see.
你能让他吃下蝙蝠吗
Do you think you could get him to eat a bat?